{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854736527","data":{"timestamp":" 947854736527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854741726","data":{"timestamp":" 947854741726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854743469","data":{"timestamp":" 947854743468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854748444","data":{"timestamp":" 947854748443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854750020","data":{"timestamp":" 947854750019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854753613","data":{"timestamp":" 947854753612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854755195","data":{"timestamp":" 947854755195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" NAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854758925","data":{"timestamp":" 947854758925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854760495","data":{"timestamp":" 947854760495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nalo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALO"," userResponse":" NALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854764069","data":{"timestamp":" 947854764068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nalo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854765623","data":{"timestamp":" 947854765622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854769137","data":{"timestamp":" 947854769137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854770723","data":{"timestamp":" 947854770723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854773465","data":{"timestamp":" 947854773465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854775056","data":{"timestamp":" 947854775055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854778665","data":{"timestamp":" 947854778665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854780245","data":{"timestamp":" 947854780245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854796110","data":{"timestamp":" 947854796109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.na.rand.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854796248","data":{"timestamp":" 947854796248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854796447","data":{"timestamp":" 947854796447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_155805"," gameId":" 86528248-722f-4fbd-bb92-718889a16ff1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.na.rand.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}